3, 2, 1, sing it out loud and reach out
Yeah, it's OK
Recently I've been dreaming of a dream that I've been dreaming of
In the middle of the original dance dance dance! Dance! Dance! It's not a joke
But surely the world
Is a special place
With a lot of
People
Dyeing their hair
And then the future is decided
Even if it doesn't bloom
The absolute one I'll be excited
Oh yeah yeah
I wanted to be more
I've grown bigger
My heart's size
My own standard
Ready? OK! Yeah! Game on stage! I'm ready, yeah, yeah, all stage
I'll stop pretending to be brave
I'm ready, yeah, yeah, everyday
So look to the right, look, it's amazing
Bow, bow, bow, if you're dancing, bow, bow, bow
Don't stop, one more
3, 2, 1, dance, dance, dance
Come on, OK, yeah
Yes, OK
Ah, ah
I'm waiting for you to choose a makeup for me
You have to love me, bye bye bye bye
You have to say something that's not too much
I'm the only where there's no loneliness
I'm the only one who's waiting for me
I'll become stronger
I can surpass my imagination
I'll believe that I can make it happen
Tokyo OK! Yeah! Step by Step
The rest is up to your heart
One step, chain away
It's OK! Ending day
It's fine, I'm just fine
Run! Run! Run!
Don't stop, run! Pop! Pop! Pop! Don't stop, come on I'm ready to dance Run Run Run If you're gonna dance, then run
Pong Pong Pong
Before that, 3, 2, 1
So let's go
Yes, OK Let's go, let's get excited
Let's dance, let's dance
In the wind of God Let's dance, let's dance
Oh baby yeah
Don't be okay, yeah, get on stage
I'll stop pretending to be brave
It's okay, yeah, everyday So look, look I'll stop doing this, I'll tease you Everyday
So look, look, it's amazing
Run, run, run, if you're dancing, dance
Bum, bum, bum, don't stop, woo, woo
3, 2, 1, time's up, let's dance
And today's MCs are Yagi Shiori and Yofu Runo from Tsubaki Factory.
We'll be sending out like this, so please stay tuned until the end.
Tsubaki Factory's new single, Baby Spider, and Kodou OK! have been released today!
It's been 11 months since the release of the single, but Ninnuma Ninuma, who graduated in June, also participated.
Especially, the music video shooting for the youth EXA-byte was the last music video shooting by Kisora Ninuma.
At the end, I shot the ending scene saying,
I'm going to break it.
I realized that it was the last scene, and I started to cry.
In the beginning, we watched the video of the song called
This video is a very sparkling song, so our performance and expression are very sparkling.
Especially Shinmen's singing and dancing, there are many outstanding parts, so please watch them a lot. This is my goat. It was chosen as the first selection for the dry dance.
How do you say that?
First, YURU MURATA danced in the center.
And then MAU AKIYAMA and my goat joined.
My goat has been taking dance lessons for a long time, so I'm happy that I was able to choose the selection.
I'm glad I did my best.
Murata Yu-chan is also very good at dancing, so I'm looking forward to working with Akiy I'll do my best as a dance member.
Please watch this video.
please.
I'm MIYAVI.
Hello KITCHEN has started.
This time, I asked this member to come.
Hello, I'm Akari Endo of JUICE JUICE.
I will do my best today.
Thank you.
Thank you, teacher.
What are you going to make this time?
Yes, I will make a grilled bibimbap.
I love it. How is it?
Do you like it?
I love grilled bibimbap.
It's delicious, isn't it?
Here are the ingredients.
So, how do you usually cook?
I don't usually cook at all.
I can't cook, but I'm going to learn a lot today.
Please.
If you have any questions, please ask the teacher.
I will do my best.
Please ask the teacher.
What should we do first?
First of all, you have to cook the rice.
This takes the most time.
It may be a little too much for one person, but the stone grill I prepared today is quite big, so it may fit in.
It's in.
I want to put some oil in here.
I want to coat the rice.
1 teaspoon.
This is the rice Yes. Start!
Okay.
This is all the ingredients for the Ishiaki Mimimba.
Namul!
Yes, it's important.
I love namul.
It's delicious.
It's a little troublesome, so I bought it at the supermarket.
You buy it, right?
I do a lot of things, but I'll make it all today.
Wow, it's hard, but let's do our best.
I'll do my best. It's hard, but let's do our best. Let's do our best.
First, the carrot.
Yes.
Do you usually help yourself without cooking?
I've made curry before.
Then you use carrots.
I used carrots.
I want to make it about this length, so I cut it into 1 3rd pieces.
Cut it into thin slices.
This will make it more stable. So it's a little difficult. Akari seems to have a favorite food.
Oh!
One is...
Carrot?
One is that she likes spicy food.
Since we're at Bibimbap today, it's a little spicy, isn't it?
That's right.
What kind of spicy food do you like?
I like Marlatan.
I usually go to Juice Juice with my friends, but I also go with my colleagues and seniors.
It's like a spring meal, and it's probably lower in calories than noodles.
That's why there are many women. I think the number of women is lower than men.
When I'm tired after a concert, I eat spicy food.
Do you want to eat spicy food?
We often go to the rehearsal after the concert.
I see.
You're good.
It's okay if the size is a little different.
That's probably better.
I'll keep it in the fridge.
Next is...
The whole grain rice.
It's a little watery, so I can eat it as it is, but it's a little long.
Cut it a little too big. Let's cut it into bite-sized pieces.
Please line them up.
Line them up.
Please cut them into bite-sized pieces.
Akari, do you like this?
I like it.
I heard you like it.
I'll put some more.
I'll put little more.
I will add a little more.
Today's namul is almost this pattern.
Salt, ground sesame seeds, sesame oil.
This is almost the same.
This is almost the same. This is almost done. Almost done. It's done when you put it on the plate.
It's easy.
I'll have a little more.
Is that enough?
Please try one.
I like it.
How is it? It's good. It's good. It's good. It's good.
It's good.
It's good. It's good. It's good. It's good. It's about half the amount of soy sauce. It's pretty salty. If you don't add this much bean sprouts, it won't taste good.
Watery bean sprouts are bad.
Can I put bean sprouts in?
Yes, please.
I will put the timer on.
I'm going to put it in.
How is it?
It's okay.
I will mix it lightly.
Salt.
And ground sesame seeds.
Before adding the oil, I want to add a little secret seasoning.
Secret seasoning?
Katsuo dashi.
A little bit.
Let's do that.
Mix it well. mix it lightly.
If you leave it alone, the taste will soak in.
Next is the spinach.
Spinach is very small, so it's okay to go this far.
It's soft.
Spinach has important points.
Miyabizu points here.
Boil the spinach as it is without cutting it.
Please go as it is. I'll put it in the middle. Just like this. Just like this.
This one is thick and strong, so I'll put this one in a long way and then I'll put it in the end.
I want you to do this.
Let's put it in.
Start.
Put it in.
All of them.
Is spinach made of iron?
Yes, it is.
Akari likes ice cream.
So she eats one every day.
I heard that recently.
You really like eating every day, don't you?
I love it.
I have ice cream on my autograph.
Really?
You have ice cream on your autograph?
Yes.
Please write it down.
I think it's natural for fans to say that.
She has ice cream on her autograph.
Really?
It's ice cream.
It's cute. It's ice cream! Cute!
What is ice cream?
Ice cream is ice cream!
I see!
It's not really entangled. It seems to be entangled around here.
I see.
I wanted to put ice cream in it.
But it's cute!
Nice. Ice love. I can ice cream.
Thank you.
I prepared the whole.
Cut the whole length of the bean sprouts and bean sprouts.
Spread the salt on the whole.
Do you eat ice cream at convenience stores?
I eat it. Do you eat ice cream at convenience stores? I do. I often go to convenience stores before going to work.
I eat ice cream and go to the meeting place.
I love it.
It's like a daily routine.
I see.
Sometimes I don't have to I sometimes say good morning without rushing.
Eating ice cream.
That's a character.
Really?
I appeared while eating ice cream today.
That's amazing.
I'm sorry. I didn't say it.
It's over in a flash.
It's done.
It's over when I noticed.
So this time it's over.
That's it.
Next time it's done.
Let's do our best.
Please look forward to it.
Let's do one more time.
I'll do it.
Yes.
Oh, it's pretty good.
Oh, good sound.
Hmm.
Delicious.
It's really good.
Wow.
Great success. Yes. It's the best. It's a great success.
It's the best I've ever eaten.
This is Yagi Shiori of Tsubaki Factory and Yohui Runo.
From now on, we will talk about each other.
I will ask you some questions, so please's answer them quickly without thinking too much!
Let's do our best!
Today is the release day of the new single.
Speaking of the typical behavior on important days such as release days,
Listen to music!
What do you want to buy now, in addition to the released Baby Spider?
Headphones There are 3 more shows left in the summer of Hello Project 2024.
What do you think of first when you look back on the past?
I made a lot of friends
What is the next candy you want to make?
Meringue cookies
What is the perfect word for Tsubaki Factory?
Chameleon.
Thank you.
Who made your friends? First of all, I have a lot of friends to talk to.
For example, I have a friend called Hana Goto.
I have talked to her a lot before,sided, but I personally like the dance of Jyusujyus' Rei Inoue.
I was happy to talk to her.
It was interesting to see you two getting along.
The perfect word for Tsubaki Factory is Chameleon.
This is the same for this single, but there are many different types of songs in Tsubaki Factory.
That's right. I want to be a chameleon who can change the color of any song.
Chameleon.
That's good.
Thank you very much.
After the VTR, Shiori's question.
Hello, STAY. Hello! Stay! Leta, leta, leta Don't choose, don't choose, leave it to me
Tsubaki Factory's new single
Youth EXO-BITE
Now on sale!
Are you ready?
Yeah, yeah, I'll stay
I'll stop pretending to be brave
Tsubaki Factory's new single
Kodou OK!
Now on sale!
Hello! Project New Member Audition 2024!
Hello! Project, which has been celebrating its 27th year this year, is recruiting new members!
The path that all Hello! Pro members have experienced is...
Audition! What's important is to take a step forward with courage! The path that everyone in the industry has experienced is the audition.
What's important is to take a step forward with courage.
We will support you with all our efforts.
This time, the audition will be held in two categories.
If you like singing, dancing, and Hello Project, you will be in the Hello Project is your favorite! If you are, please join the Hello Project department!
And if you want to show off your talents and your own personality,
please join the Beyonds Potential department!
Will you make your dreams come true with us at Hello Project?
We are waiting for your application!
We are waiting for your applications!
Next, I will ask Yagi Shiori-chan a question. I'll do my best!
Yes.
Every month, the 28th is the day of the chicken.
What is your favorite Yagi-meshi tamago-ryouri?
Tamagoyaki!
Currently, during the application period during the new members audition?
Singing the opera Aria!
What is the subject you want to film with a camera?
All the members of the All of Us and the Shakunetsu no Tsub OF US. What do you do before going to bed?
Yoga.
Yoga?
Sometimes.
This month, you will hold the 3rd anniversary event of the RITU CAM.
Please say a word on that day.
I'm a fan.
Thank you.
Currently, it is in the application period of the new member audition 2024.
Yagishi-Ori said that she sang the opera aria while she was still in the memory of the audition.
I learned vocal music, and even those who are doing it so seriously are among those who receive idols.
I thought it would be easy to remember that it might be a little less, so I sang it, but the moment I sang it, the judges were completely different.
I thought it was a good answer, so everyone is the only one.
If you have something that you don't have, you're better than the other people who are auditioning. and I think that I'm better at this than others.
I want you to take that as your strength and take it to the audition.
Do you have any advice from RUNO?
My advice is that I think it's really about showing yourself.
So don't think too much and just show your true self.
That's why people ask me questions.
I think you have natural to think deeply about what you want to do and what you want to change.
I think it's good to think deeply and return what you think.
Thank you.
Hello! Project New Member Audition 2024 is currently in progress.
The deadline for application is from September 2nd to Monday 10 am on Monday. I hope you can apply with confidence with this advice.
I'm Nina Hayashi, 13 years old.
I wanted to learn singing and dancing, so I was looking for it myself My mother recommended me to audition for the HELLO PROJECT.
I've been doing this for about a year and a half.
I had a new encounter and a lot of tough things.
I have a goal to achieve my dreams.
I can aim for that kind of thing. I have a goal and so I can aim for that.
I have a goal and I can do my best.
I'm YAMAZUKI MEI of Morning Musume 2.4 and KOBAYASHI HONOKA of BEYOND.
YAMAZUKI has a great singing, dancing and the style of the dance. Kobayashi is very good at drawing and playing the piano.
That's what I admire about him.
I'm a beat planet.
My specialty is the hula hoop.
I learned it when I was in the gym.
I think I often use the back of my head and often used to turn the body with the waist.
I was taught to spread my arms like this and use the back of my shoulders to flow from here to here.
I was very happy when I did that and I did it many times.
Debut with Hello Project.
English.
It's the most common subject among the 9 subjects.
I like it because I'm good at it.
Is it STOP?
I couldn't remember STOP at all for a while.
I was trying to remember the word stop from my friend.
I kept saying stop.
Then it became my favorite word in English.
I'm said to be a positive person.
I'm too positive and sometimes I can't stop.
I think that's one of my characteristics.
So I accept it.
I want to go to Shanghai. I want to go to Shanghai.
I've always wanted to go to theme parks, but I've never been abroad, so I want to go to China.
Collecting miniatures.
I love miniatures, so I'll talk about three things I like about them.
First, I can compare my own miniatures to those of others.
The packaging and the back are all very realistic.
I like to look at those details, so I like to see the details of the real thing.
The second is that I can see the elegance of my hands.
I don't think I touch small things. I can feel how small it is by touching it.
I can also see the size of my hand.
The third is to be able to collect a lot of things you like.
There are various types of things.
There is also a sofa. There are many different types of clothes, especially sofas.
The texture is also very realistic.
The most attractive thing about the miniature is that I can make very high sounds with, so I chose Platonic Planet, which has a high sound from low to high.
My teacher told me that I don't have a sense of body, and if I don't have a sense of body, I'll have a bad singing. I hope you can listen to my songs and improve your singing skills.
I want to train my body and soul.
I want to use my songs and train my body and soul.
I want to move on to my dreams. I'm better than the world I'll hug you with my heart
I'll hug you with my heart
I won't forgive everything
This time's Hello! Pro training session was with Hayashi Nina-chan
Hayashi Nina-chan is from Aichifecture, so we're from the same place.
I often talk about it.
The performance of the first beat of the training announcement was very memorable.
The high pitch of the voice is very high-pitched, and I thought she would become a great idol.
I've talked to Nina Hayashi several times.
We went to the performance performance for the test,
I talked about the performance of Hayashi Nina-chan.
It was a great performance. So when I said, I was so happy to hear that she said,
Thank you very much! I will do my best again!
She was so bright
and I thought she was a wonderful girl
so I wanted to talk to her more
Please look forward to the next HaruPro training session!
Hello! Stay!
I'm Shiori Yagi from Tsubaki Factory
and I'm Haro, a host of FF-Runo
Today, on August 28th, I'm Shiori Yagi from Tsubaki Factory And I'm Haroste from FF-Runo
Today, August 28th, is the release day of Tsubaki Factory's new single
Tomorrow, August 29th, the summer festival of Tsubaki Factory, 2024 Shakunetsu
Will be held at Kawaguchi Costella Theater
Yay! We are holding this event for the first time in 3 years.
I would like to introduce the most memorable scene from the past 2 years.
The most memorable scene for me is the first time we performed Rainbow Pink.
Wow, you've heard of it. The song Rainbow Pink was performed by Kiki Asakura and Saori Onoda in the shuffle unit.
The two are in peach and light pink, and the member color is pink.
The song Rainbow Pink matches the member color.
And this song is really cute. It's cute. The song Pink is also a good match for the members.
And this song is really cute. It's cute.
The intro part is also cute.
The song is also cute.
We sang together for a while.
After we saw the song I also tried to make rainbow blue.
So, I was impressed by the rainbow pink that became popular for a while.
How about you, ZUNO?
I think it's more about the overall than the scene.
We can think of clothes our own costumes every year.
And since it's a year-end event, we can create our own unique costumes.
We can only create our own.
That's why I'm looking forward to what will happen this year.
Also, we have new members, so I'm looking forward to seeing her outfit.
We've looked back at the past two years of heat,
what kind of live will this heat be?
This heat is like this every time,
there is a corner where solo, duo, and trio are divided.
The new members have not had the opportunity to play at Hina Fest, so I'm looking forward to seeing the trio, duo, and solo. I think it will be. In the subchannel of Tsubaki Factory, the I hope the audience will also look forward to it.
I will be participating in the Japanese Taiko show that I have been doing since last year.
This year, Ono Mizuho, Shiori Yagi, Isshimi Hane, Yui Murata, andifuka, and these five will be participating.
Mizuho from Watashi-Yagi will continue from last year,
and the three main members will start from this year.
So please look forward to the great performance.
Actually, I've been playing Wadaiko for about 7 or 8 years since I was in elementary school.
That's a long time. I've been doing Japanese music for about 7 or 8 years since I was in sixth grade.
I didn't tell you much about it.
I almost forgot about it myself.
I'm surprisingly good at it.
I hope you can enjoy it.
Finally, let's go with this song! Heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, heart, I'm not going to let you go Don't be nervous If she comes
You can go there
Shara shara shara shara
Don't run away
I'm nervous
Who are you talking to?
Don't be so shy I'm telling you I'm telling you I'm telling you
I won't forgive you for being a coward
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you
I love you, I love you I love you, I love you I love you, I love you I love you, I love you I love you, I love you Special Generation I want to believe in destiny
Even if it's a million years away
This love is courage
Special Generation
I can't be a pretty girl
Even if I'm in the subway
I love you loved than ever
As I
Whoa, whoa, yeah
Change the version
Atta, atta, wherever you go, I'm always looking for you
I'm the only one who can't find you
There's no way I can win
I'm a little bit nervous
I'm a little bit nervous I'm a little bit nervous I'm a little bit nervous I'm a little bit nervous Let's go together Let's go together Let's go together
Everyone is surprised
I'm the one who's the hottest
Girls
Special
Specialization
Specialization I can't feel my heart
Even if it's too hard to go
This line is the end
Special Generation Challenge
I won't let go, I won't let go
More than yesterday, more than now
Love tomorrow too I won't let go More than yesterday, more than now
I love tomorrow too
Special Generation
I don't feel lonely
Even if I'm dead
This love is eternal
Special Generation
I can't let go, I won't let go
More than yesterday, more than now
I'll do it again
I love you I'm the new generation I'm the new generation
New generation
I'm the new generation
Let's do our best tomorrow!
This is Yagi Shiori from Tsubaki Factory and Hello Stay, brought to you by YAHEI RUNA.
It's time to say goodbye.
Here's a news.
Today's new single, Baby Spider,
and the youth EXO-Bite KODO OK! are released.
All three songs are wonderful songs,
so I hope you all enjoy them.
Tomorrow, at the Kaw Factory Summer Festival 2024 will be held at Kawaguchi Kostera Theater.
It's a very exciting and hot concert, so please come and see it.
Hello! Project 2024 Summer All of Us Rega Altair is being held. and the next one is the The concert will be held at Nagoya Park this weekend
It's a little sad to be separated from everyone
but we want to enjoy the last concert as much as possible
From September 8th, the live tour of TSUBAKI FACTORY 2024 will be held
For us, it's our first live house tour
so we want to enjoy it.
And the new member audition for Hello Project 2024 is being held.
The deadline for the application is from September 2nd to Monday 10am.
Let's have a great time together!
We are waiting for your application!
Hello! Step is a channel where the! Project members appear more and more.
New videos are uploaded every Wednesday, so please give us a high rating, comment, and subscribe to our channel.
This time, we were Yagishi Ori and Yohero Luna from Tsubaki Factory.
Goodbye! This was Yuna. Sayonara!